(words typing and beeping)
(static buzzing)
- Earth to Mars.
Lander report status, please.
- Mars Lander here.
Gravity device status effective.
Oxygen status 98%.
- Any sign of habitation?
- Not so much as a, whoa, there, horsey.
What the?
- Cute. What is it?
- Oh, it's cute all right.
It couldn't be.
(ground rumbling)
- Mars Lander, what's happening up there?
(dramatic music)
(upbeat pop music)
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I think I did it again ♪
♪ I made believe we're
more than just friends ♪
♪ Oh, baby, it might seem like a crush ♪
♪ But it doesn't mean that I'm serious ♪
♪ Because to lose all my senses ♪
♪ That is just so typically me ♪
♪ Oh baby, baby ♪
♪ Oops, I did it again ♪
♪ I played with your heart ♪
♪ Got lost in the game ♪
♪ Oh baby, baby ♪
♪ Oops, you think I'm in love ♪
♪ That I'm sent from above ♪
♪ I'm not that innocent ♪
♪ You see, my problem is this ♪
♪ I'm dreaming away ♪
♪ Wishing that heroes, they truly exist ♪
♪ I cry watching the days ♪
♪ Can't you see I'm a
fool in so many ways ♪
♪ But to lose all my senses ♪
♪ That is just so typically me ♪
♪ Oh baby, oh ♪
♪ Oops, I did it again ♪
♪ I played with your heart ♪
♪ Got lost in the game ♪
♪ Oh baby, baby ♪
♪ Oops, you think I'm in love ♪
♪ That I'm sent from above ♪
♪ I'm not that innocent ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
(gentle bells)
- All aboard!
- Britney, before you go,
there's something I want you to have.
- Oh, it's beautiful.
But wait a minute. Isn't this...
- Yeah. Yes, it is.
- But I thought the old lady dropped it
into the ocean in the end.
- Well, baby, I went
down and got it for you.
- Oh, you shouldn't have.
♪ Oops, I did it again to your heart ♪
♪ Got lost in this game, oh, baby ♪
♪ Oops, you think that
I'm sent from above ♪
♪ I'm not that innocent ♪
♪ Oops, I did it again ♪
♪ I played with your heart ♪
♪ Got lost in the game ♪
♪ Oh baby, baby ♪
♪ Oops, you think I'm in love ♪
♪ That I'm sent from above ♪
♪ I'm not that innocent ♪
♪ Oops, I did it again ♪
♪ I played with your heart ♪
♪ Got lost in the game ♪
♪ Oh baby, baby ♪
♪ Oops, you think I'm in love ♪
♪ That I'm sent from above ♪
♪ I'm not that innocent ♪